{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Residential \u0026 Commercial Locksmiths","appliedActionRules":{"SDB_SCROLLY_SITE_24719":"SDB_SCROLLY_SITE_24719_ctrl"},"categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/40097/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40097,"taskName":"Locksmith","taskDescription":"Find a Locksmith Service","xmTaskDescriptor":"Residential \u0026 Commercial Locksmiths","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":155,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Locksmith keying master make keys","textMessagingName":"Locksmith","rolloverLongDesc":"Home Locksmiths fix, replace or reconfigure all kinds of locks \u0026 door latches. They also re-key locks \u0026 make keys.","rolloverShortDesc":"Includes associated latches, knobs \u0026 hardware.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local Locksmith Services. HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated locksmiths in your area.","htmlTitle":"Residential \u0026 Commercial Locksmith \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Key \u0026 Lock Services","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":49,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Locksmith","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Locksmith - Home","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Locksmith Need","urlName":"Locksmith","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Residential \u0026 Commercial Locksmiths - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor","searchKeywords":"Locksmith,keying,master,make,keys,lost,locksmiths,locksmithing,door,deadbolt,locks,Lockout","emcCategoryOid":-12048,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":409,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564376528849pwspr012F22724D8FA4DFF8FD65C05DD318E5A42.pwspr009-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40097/":{"taskOID":40097,"originalTaskOID":40097,"setID":409,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":501096,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Lock","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Where do you need service?","shortQuestionText":"Where do you need service?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":201517,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home / Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home / Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":201518,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business / Commercial","answerDisplayText":"Business / Commercial","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":201516,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Car / Auto","answerDisplayText":"Car / Auto","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":8152,"questionDisplayText":"Is this an emergency?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this an emergency?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501095,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Service","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of lock service do you need?","shortQuestionText":"What type of lock service do you need?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":201519,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Open a locked door","answerDisplayText":"Open a locked door","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":201520,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Install or replace existing lock(s)","answerDisplayText":"Install or replace existing lock(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5047,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Re-key existing lock(s)","answerDisplayText":"Re-key existing lock(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5210,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Repair existing lock(s)","answerDisplayText":"Repair existing lock(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11148,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Emergency Service","answerDisplayText":"Emergency Service","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":501096,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Lock","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Where do you need service?","shortQuestionText":"Where do you need service?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":201517,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home / Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home / Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":201518,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business / Commercial","answerDisplayText":"Business / Commercial","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":201516,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Car / Auto","answerDisplayText":"Car / Auto","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":201517,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home / Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home / Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":201518,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business / Commercial","answerDisplayText":"Business / Commercial","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":201516,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Car / Auto","answerDisplayText":"Car / Auto","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":8152,"questionDisplayText":"Is this an emergency?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this an emergency?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501095,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Service","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of lock service do you need?","shortQuestionText":"What type of lock service do you need?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":201519,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Open a locked door","answerDisplayText":"Open a locked door","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":201520,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Install or replace existing lock(s)","answerDisplayText":"Install or replace existing lock(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5047,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Re-key existing lock(s)","answerDisplayText":"Re-key existing lock(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5210,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Repair existing lock(s)","answerDisplayText":"Repair existing lock(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":201519,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Open a locked door","answerDisplayText":"Open a locked door","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":201520,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Install or replace existing lock(s)","answerDisplayText":"Install or replace existing lock(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5047,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Re-key existing lock(s)","answerDisplayText":"Re-key existing lock(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5210,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Repair existing lock(s)","answerDisplayText":"Repair existing lock(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11148,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Emergency Service","answerDisplayText":"Emergency Service","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11148,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Emergency Service","answerDisplayText":"Emergency Service","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]}]}}